KAYE DANTE

WEB DEVELOPER



- 0439370009
- k.flamenco89@gmail.com
- Perth. West Australia
- linkedin.com/in/kayemdante
- https://github.com/KayeDante89

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Kaye, a passionate creator hailing from the Philippines and currently based in Perth, WA. I have always had a profound love for the world of tech and the arts. I have a background as a Graphic Designer and am currently honing my skills in Front End Development so I can continue to create visually stunning digital experiences.

SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | JS
- React | Typescript | Liquid
- Photoshop | InDesign | Illustrator
- **Customer Service**
- Organisation
- Team Work
- Leadership

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER / TECH SUPPORT

Hustle | Incubator

2023 - Present

- Tech Support / Shopify Web Dev
- Frontend Developer | React/TypeScript

TEAM LEADER | RETAIL BUYER

Dymocks Hay Street

2015 - 2023

- Customer Service | Team Leader (Assistant Manager)
- Receiver | Retail Buyer (handling stock levels)
- Team Leader / Assistant Manager

EDUCATION

SHE CODES AUS

She Codes Plus

2022 - 2023

CENTRAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Cert IV in Design [Graphic Design] 2013

REFERENCE

LAURA BIGGS (Recruiter for Hustle)



0433145120

STEWART BIRD (Previous Manager at Dymocks Hay St)



0422 561 522